drive-now.com 2016-03-28

# 

                                  BMW CAR SHARING LLC
                                     PRIVACY POLICY
         1.     Introduction. BMW Car Sharing, LLC (“BMWCS”) provides car sharing
services in certain cities in the United States by making BMW and MINI vehicles
(including BMW electric vehicles) available to people who meet its membership criteria
and are approved as members. You must apply for membership, be authorized by
BMWCS and enter into a Membership Agreement with BMWCS (the “Membership
Agreement”) before reserving or operating any BMWCS vehicle.
         2.     Scope. BMWCS appreciates the trust you place in us and does not want
to jeopardize that trust. We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting the
security of your personal information. This Privacy Policy applies to the BMWCS
website, located at www.bmwcarsharing.com (the “Website”) and the BMWCS mobile
application (the “App”) and other websites or applications that link to or display this
Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Technology Platform”). By accessing or using the
Technology Platform, you hereby consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and
the BMWCS Mobile Application and Website Terms of Use (the “Terms of Use”).
If you do not consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and Terms of Use, please do
not use our Technology Platform, products or services.
         3.     What Information Does [BMWCS] Collect? As part of evaluating your
application to join BMWCS and providing you with our products and services, we, and
third parties engaged by us, obtain personally identifiable information about you
including, but not limited to, your first and last name, home or other physical address,
email address, phone number, date of birth, drivers’ license information, personal photo,
and credit card information. As part of the application process for joining BMWCS, we,
or a third party engaged by us, will also run a Driver Record Check (as defined in the
Membership Agreement) on you. We may also collect information from you as
described in Section 6 below.
         4.     How Does [BMWCS] Use My Information? Our primary goals in
collecting personally identifiable information from you are to: (a) enable us to approve or
disapprove your membership status (on an ongoing basis) in accordance with the
Membership Qualification Standards (as defined in the Membership Agreement); (b)
facilitate efficient transactions; and (c) provide you with information regarding relevant
products and services. We may also use information we collect from you to improve or
develop new products, services or websites; conduct research or analysis; comply with
legal requirements; or other purposes. We, or third parties engaged by us, may store
any information we collect from you.
         5.     What Information Does [BMWCS] Share? We will share personally
identifiable information with certain third parties in order to process your application to

join BMWCS and as part of providing you with our products and services. For example,
we may share personally identifiable information with members of the BMW Group or
any subsidiaries of any member of the BMW Group who may assist us in providing
offers for products or services that may be of interest to you. Members of the BMW
Group include, but are not limited to, BMW AG, BMW of North America, BMW Financial
Services, BMW Bank of North America and BMW Insurance Agency. We may also
share personally identifiable information with non-affiliated companies that market our
products and services, such as our retail centers who are distinct entities and have their
own privacy policies. We may also share information about you and your reservation
and use of rental vehicles with law enforcement officials or other third parties in
connection with traffic and parking violation citations; accident reports; tolls; and other
citations, violations, fines, or similar items. We may also share personally identifiable
information with non-affiliated companies that provide services on our behalf (including,
but not limited to, insurance companies, customer support companies, mail fulfillment
companies, or identification verification companies). For example, we have engaged
Jumio, an identification credentials authentication company, to verify the identification
you submit to us and so we will share information submitted by you to Jumio including,
but not limited to, the information contained on, and an image of, your driver’s license
and a comparison photo. Jumio may store these images and information. The third
parties listed in this Section 5 are not exclusive. We may engage other third parties to
assist us with providing you with our products and services from time to time, without
notice to you, and we may share any and all information we collect from you with such
third parties subject to applicable law.
        6.     Confidentiality. In certain areas of the Technology Platform you may
choose to share personal information with us, such as your name, address or even your
driving interests. We may use this information for marketing research and other
marketing and service related purposes like sending brochures you request and
keeping in touch by email. Where required or permitted by law, we may share your
personal information with our related companies, our business partners or others. We
may transfer information about you to a company that acquires the assets of [BMWCS]
or one of our business units, for example, as a result of a sale, merger, reorganization
or liquidation. Customer telephone calls may be recorded to protect you and our staff.
        7.     Registration and Personal Settings. Before you may reserve a car, you
must register and be approved as a member and enter into a Membership Agreement.
Registered members may access the reservation system and correct or update their
personal information by entering their login ID and password. To edit, delete or add to
information you have shared while visiting our Technology Platform, log in and go to the
[General and Personal Data] section. If you notify us that any information you provided
us (such as ZIP code or email address) has changed, we will endeavor to correct or
update your personal data. If your membership of BMWCS is terminated for any reason,
we may keep the information we have collected from you for a period of time to be
determined in our sole discretion subject to applicable law. Additionally, the information
you include in a registration or reservation request is secure while in transit to us.
                                               2

      8.      Cookies, Web Beacons, Advertisements, and Other Automated
Information Collection. We use browser cookies, web beacons, logs and other
technologies for analytics, functionality, convenience, marketing, security or other
purposes relating to your use of our websites, applications, products or services.
              8.1    Cookies: Cookies produce a luxury and convenience similar to that
      of memory seats. They save you the trouble of reentering certain information in
      some registration areas, help to deliver content specific information to you and
      track which sections of the site are most popular. The cookies we use are
      elements of data stored by your browser on your device. We use browser
      cookies to authenticate you; track your session; remember settings, location or
      preferences; for advertising and conversion tracking; or provide other functions.
      You may set your browser settings to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie
      is placed on your device. The [Help] portion of your browser should explain how
      to configure your browser’s cookie handling. You may have limited functionality if
      you block browser cookies set by our websites.
              8.2    Web Beacons: Web beacons are objects placed on web pages
      that allow us to determine whether and for how long you view web pages. We
      use web beacons for site traffic reporting, auditing and reporting, personalization,
      unique visitor counts, advertising, conversion tracking or other functions. Your
      web browser may have add-ons that may help you to manage web beacons.
      You may have limited functionality if you block web beacons set by our websites.
              8.3    Third Party Service Providers: We may use third-party service
      providers to provide us information, analysis and reports about the use of our
      websites and to enable you to interact with us or other users of our products,
      services or websites. We may use various web technologies from Google,
      Facebook, Twitter, Optimizely or others.
              8.4    Advertisements: We may use third-party service providers to
      provide us advertising, marketing, conversion tracking or other information and
      services. We may use various web technologies from Microsoft Atlas, Rocket
      Fuel or others. You may find out more information about these technologies and
      your choices by using the Digital Advertising Alliance opt-out page here, Network
      Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page here or Interactive Advertising Bureau EU
      page here.
              8.5    Logs:    We use log information relating to Internet Protocol
      addresses, web requests, date and time of your request, operating systems,
      browser types, browser languages and cookies that may uniquely identify your
      browser or your device. We use this information to administer our systems;
      diagnose problems; provide analytics; enhance the functionality of our products,
      services or websites; or to make our products, services or websites more
      convenient, secure or efficient.
                                            3

              8.6    Other Automated Collection: We may also collect automated
        information through technologies built into our mobile application software.
        These technologies may gather information on how you interact with our
        products or services.
        9.    Subscriptions/Newsletters.        Except for communications related to
registration or reservations or in response to a specific request from you, you will only
receive emails or mailings from BMWCS if you have requested to be on our
correspondence list. If you are currently on our list and do not wish to receive further
information from us, simply click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the
correspondence.
        10.   Links. Though our Technology Platform may contain links to other sites,
we are not responsible for the content, links or privacy on any of those sites.
        11.   Email Links. We may use email links throughout the Technology
Platform to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may
have. We read every message and try to reply promptly to everyone. Information in the
message may be used to respond directly to your comments or questions. We may
also file your comments to improve the Technology Platform and programs, or review
and discard the information.
        12.   Questions. BMWCS, located at 95 Morton Street, New York, NY 10014
is the data controller responsible for the processing of your information. If you have
further questions about our Privacy Policy, the practices of our Technology Platform or
your experience with our Technology Platform, contact us at info@bmwcarsharing.com
or 844-732-2466.
        13.   Revisions. We may change our Privacy Policy and/or Terms of Use on
one or more occasions by posting a revised policy on the Technology Platform. When
we post changes, we will revise the “Last Updated” date above. The revised version will
be effective on the “Effective Date” above. If the revised version includes substantial
changes, we will attempt to provide you with 30 days’ prior notice by posting the revised
version at least 30 days before the Effective Date. We encourage you to frequently
review this Privacy Policy and Terms of Use for changes. Your continued use of the
Technology Platform after we make changes is deemed to be an acceptance of those
changes to the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use.
                                             4
